Dear Sir/Madam,

Hope this mail finds you well. I am writing to express my interest in joining your company as **Digital Marketing Manager.**

Since online digital marketing and e-commerce has been an integral part of my working experiences for more than 4 years, I wish to learn and develop the other path of online digital marketing in your company.

My working experiences are quiet involved with certain e-commerce and digital marketing stuffs as I used to work as *Corporate E-Commerce Executive* at *Corporate Santika Indonesia Hotels & Resorts* and as *Digital Marketing Executive* at *Starwood International Hotels & Resorts* (placed in Sheraton Grand Jakarta Gandaria City).

During my work, I have been managing online distribution for more than 75 Santika & Amaris Hotel properties all across Indonesia. And with Starwood Hotels, I have learn more further about other *digital* platforms, display media campaign, content marketing, social media optimization, social media marketing, programatic buy and etc.

I believe that to be a part of your big team will become a great opportunity to gain my knowledge and ability in digital channel, and networking in a greater scale.

I can manage my work under pressured, able to work in a team or individually, and willing to take a bigger challenge.

Please find the enclosed file of my resume to provide you more information about my strengths, achievements, and qualifications.

Looking forward to have an opportunity to meet or talk with you regarding my application to your established company.

Thank you for your consideration and opportunity:)

Sincerely,

Edvan Prima Yoga

Edvan Prima Yoga



Digital Marketing Executive at Sheraton Grand Jakarta Gandaria City

Email: edvanprimayoga@gmail.com / Mobile: +62812 3000 6952

Summary

I have over 4 years of experience working in Digital Marketing field.

Currently, I work as **Digital Marketing Executive** at Sheraton Jakarta Gandaria City Hotel, improving products and services for our customers by using advanced online digital platforms, standing up big-data analytical tools, creating and maintaining promotions and contents on social media, and onboarding compelling new data sets.

Competencies: Digital Marketing, Online Booking, Social Media, Website CMS, & Booking Engine.

Experience

Digital Marketing Executive (Pre-Opening Team) at Sheraton Grand Jakarta Gandaria City March 2015 - Present

Corporate E-Commerce Executive at Santika Indonesia Hotels & Resorts

March 2013 - February 2015

Languages:

- Bahasa Indonesia
- English
- Italiano

Skills & Expertise

- E-commerce
- Digital Marketing
- Search Engine Optimization
- Search Engine Marketing
- Website Development
- Online Reputation Management
- Social Media
- Booking Engine

Education

• Istituto Italiano di Cultura Jakarta

Italian Language and Literature, 2010 - 2012

Grade: Intermediate

STP SAHID

Bachelor of Applied Science (B.A.Sc.), Tourism and Travel Services Management, 2009 - 2013 Activities and Societies: STFC Futsal Team as Team Leader.

SMKN 57 JAKARTA

High School, Hospitality Industries, 2004 - 2007

Activities and Societies: English Debate. Inter School Student Organitation.

Certifications

Social Media DeepDive by Kompas Gramedia

KOMPAS GRAMEDIA September 2014

Pre- Opening Team (Sheraton Grand Jakarta Gandaria City Hotel)

Starwood Hotels & Resorts Worldwide, Inc. October 2015

HOTSTARTS Digital Marketing Strategy – Asia Pacific

Starwood Hotels & Resorts Worldwide, Inc. April 2016

Projects

E-Commerce Workshop Santika Internet Booking Engine 2.0

November 2014 to November 2014

Santika Online Reputation Management (via TrustYou)

January 2014 to February 2015

Local Property Site - Sheraton Grand Jakarta Gandaria City

March 2016